<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CHI Gratitude</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_share">share</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string name="share">ShareFragment</string>
    <string name="logout">logout</string>
    <string name="information">Information</string>
    <string name="contacts">Contacts</string>
    <string name="shareto">share</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="history_CHI"><b>AIM OF CHI(HOME)</b>\n
    Inspired by the ideals and philosophy of Mahatma Gandhi, Child Haven International is a registered charity founded in 1985.\n
        We assist children and women in developing countries, who are in need of food, education,
        health care, shelter and clothing, emotional and moral support.
    "Let    me light my lamp, says the star, and never debate if it will dispel the dark" Rabindranath Tagore\n\n
        <b>OUR    STORY</b>\n\
    Child Haven has five homes in India, one in Nepal, one in Tibet in China and one in Bangladesh.
        Our homes accept children who are disabled, parentless, or
        from socially disadvantaged situations - and who are destitute, i.e. do not receive even one good meal a day.

Girls and boys are treated equally, and without regard to race, caste,
        colour, religion or culture. Living is simple and meals are vegetarian. We try not to Westernize the children,
        but rather attempt to raise them according to the highest ideals of their own cultures.
        We respect the heritage of each child, whether Hindu, Muslim, Jain, Sikh, Christian, Buddhist, secular or other.\n\n

        <b>CREATING SELF-SUFFICIENCY</b>\n
Destitute children from birth to six years of age are referred to us by local social welfare agencies.
        Child Haven Homes provide full care through high school (Tenth Standard),
        and then provide vocational training so that each child can enter the local society as a self-sufficient adult.\n\n

        <b>WOMENS PROGRAMS</b>\n
Another aspect of Child Havens Gandhian philosophy is our commitment
        to improving the condition of women through direct employment, education, medical aid, legal aid,
        and training opportunities.

Child Haven is also involved in environmentally friendly projects,
        family planning, literacy and soya milk production as a cottage industry for groups of women.First Ten Years

CHILD HAVEN THROUGH THE YEARS
1985

Child Haven incorporated in Canada as registered charitable organization
First six volunteers to India
Official opening of first Home in Dhanera, Gujarat
1986\n\n

Child Haven receives All-India Registration
Hyderabad home opens in balcony of former theatre provided rent free by State Red Cross
Formation of Ottawa and Cornwall Support Groups
1987\n\n

Child Haven granted state license for Gujarat
Hyderabad Home moved to rented house
Ottawa Support Group holds first Fundraising Dinner for benefit of eighteen month old Pinky, in need of open heart surgery\n
1988

Kaliyampoondi Home opens
Formation of Glengarry County Support Group
Formation of SoyaCow Support Group, Ottawa
Cornwall Support Group holds First Annual Dinner\n
1989

Dhanera Home moved to Changa, Gujarat
First local adoption in Gujarat
CBC sends Man Alive producer Robin Taylor and Host Peter Downie to India to film a half hour program on Child Haven\n
1990

Formation of Toronto Support Group
Toronto Group holds first Annual Dinner
CHATELAINE magazine publishes feature article on Child Haven
1991\n\n

Child Haven receives first grant from CIDA for Soya Milk Project
1992

Hyderabad Home moves to larger quarters
Child Haven purchases six SoyaCow systems for Soya Milk Cottage Industry, India
Formation of Ottawa Unitarian Support Group
Child Haven provides start-up funds for Changa Kindergarten for Child Haven and Changa village children
Child Haven receives third grant from CIDA for Soya Milk Project
1993\n\n

Kathmandu Home officially opened in Nepal
Opening of Child Haven English Medium School in Kaliyampoondi
Formation of Vancouver Support Group
Artist Pieter Doef completes over 100 oil paintings of India and Nepal. 2/3 of selling price is donated to Child Haven
First Vancouver Support Group
        Dinner Opening of SoyaCow Centre in Ghaziabad Death of
        Mr. A. K. Ramakrishna Reddiar, Gandhian mentor and village elder of Kaliyampoondi 1994\n\n

First London, Ontario Support Group Dinner
Child Haven registered as official NGO with Nepal Social Welfare Council
Start up grant for Womens Weaving Cottage Industry, Kathmandu 2002\n\n

Home in Chittagong Bangladesh opened.
2009\n

V. Kalyanam, who acted as the personal secreatry for Gandhi from 1944 until his death in 1948,
        agreed to serve as Patron of Child Haven International and board member of Child Haven International/India
2011\n\n

Hyderabad – Completed new building, with boys Dorm, office space, Assembly/Dining Hall.\n\n
2012\n\n\n

<i>Hyderabad – First bio-gas system installed
Hyderabad – New open air Study Hall, 34 x 20 between old and new building
Ankur Trust Educational Home – Soya Cow system up and running
Tibet in China – New dried yak and wood dung stove installed
Savarsai – New boys dormitory is constructed
Ghaziabadi – Installed the first sanitary napkin-making system. Inventor and Child Haven patron A. Muruganathan
    2013\n\n</i>

Diamond Jubilee Endowment Fund launch\n <b>For more details please visit our official website</b>\n
                             www.childhaven.ca\n
        <u>"The best way to prove the humanity is ,help others"</u>\n
        \n
        \n
        \n


</string>
    <string name="article_on_chi">Article</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="nav_open">Open</string>
    <string name="nav_close">Close</string>
</resources>